It's nice because I like it on purpose and I like it myself.
The first is this.
Oh, the one from earlier.
I never look away from them, and I ask them to take a picture of us staring at each other.
It makes me happy to know that there are people who blush when they see me.
I was the best in my class in modern literature.
It's very unusual to be a celebrity with a supporter.
Is it true?
How are your studies going?
Nighttime Island Idol
Well, here I am.
Actually, I was born in Tyneside and grew up in the Stardus hot water room.
Let's call today's guest.
This is your idol.
I am here to grab your crown.
I am Miyako and Yuuzu Kimiya from Crown Pop.
Pleased to meet you.
Yuzuki-san, you are here. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Speaking of Ms. Yuzuki, on February 19, a two-minute selfie video was released.
Yes, I am very happy to see it.
In the comments section of YouTube.
Shuushu is so cute. I'm already melting. And.
I'm getting more and more into the swamp of Meya every day. I'm getting more and more addicted to Meeja's swamp every day.
She is really cute.
Is it true?
Really?
Thank you very much.
I was watching it the other day.
I was watching TV Asahi's "One Man's Fundoshi.
Thank you very much.
I'm into things that come out of you.
Really?
That's amazing.
And you do it so naturally to the audience at the benefit events.
It sounds strange, but I think it's very attractive.
Thank you very much. I'm glad to hear that.
But I get nervous. I'm going to be honest.
I'm quite nervous.
That's true.
You said you are not good at talking to kettle kettles.
That's right. I get nervous talking to the kettle.
That part is a bit of a fantasy.
I am sorry.
I don't know why. Why so much?
Is it that? I don't mesh with Mizuki.
We will mesh for the rest of our lives.
Even with Mizuki, right?
No, no, I still lack adaptability in some areas.
I haven't drawn out all of them yet.
That's right. I'm thinking of adding more from now on.
Even Mizuki's idol drawer.
Yes.
That's what I mean.
Now, Mizuki, you are the youngest member of Clap, and you have a little sisterly feeling about you.
But in real life, are you a big sister with a little sister?
Yes, I have two sisters, and my younger sister is Nico.
Oh, really? What kind of sister are you?
What kind of sister?
But my mother and other people around me often tell me that my sister is more like an older sister.
Is that true? Are you actually a strong older sister behind the scenes?
I don't know. But I am a big sister in some ways.
She says, "Hey! She's the one who says, "I'm a big sister," and thinks about it all the time.
You must have worked pretty hard in school. Because I myself am.
I sometimes help my sister with her studies when she has a test coming up.
Really? That's quite unusual for a Stanhurst talent.
It's true.
How are your studies?
I thought she was doing pretty well.
In my third year of high school, I was usually first in my class in modern studies.
Oh, wow.
Yes, that's right.
Class 1?
But I heard you talking the other day on TV, and your language is very proper.
Is that true?
Yes, I am.
I am very happy.
I often go to 3B Junior and Takoyaki Rainbow.
And this show is Sura-chan.
I have Mya-chan in a corner of my heart! who is a member of
Missy-san
Miya Isseishi-san
Mr. Hiroo Gugudan
Mr. Naobo
Courtesy of
Happy day to you!
Thank you very much for your support!